<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dmodule xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../src/Schema/descript.xsd">
  <identAndStatusSection>
    <dmAddress>
      <dmIdent>
        <dmCode modelIdentCode="MALE" systemDiffCode="A" systemCode="15" subSystemCode="0" subSubSystemCode="0" assyCode="01" disassyCode="00" disassyCodeVariant="A" infoCode="018" infoCodeVariant="A" itemLocationCode="A" />
        <language languageIsoCode="en" countryIsoCode="EN" />
        <issueInfo issueNumber="000" inWork="01" />
      </dmIdent>
      <dmAddressItems>
        <issueDate year="2023" month="10" day="31" />
        <dmTitle>
          <techName>Preface</techName>
        </dmTitle>
      </dmAddressItems>
    </dmAddress>
    <dmStatus>
      <security securityClassification="01" />
      <responsiblePartnerCompany enterpriseCode="0001Z">
        <enterpriseName>PT Dirgantara Indonesia</enterpriseName>
      </responsiblePartnerCompany>
      <originator enterpriseCode="0001Z">
        <enterpriseName>PT Dirgantara Indonesia</enterpriseName>
      </originator>
      <applicCrossRefTableRef>
        <dmRef>
          <dmRefIdent>
            <dmCode modelIdentCode="MALE" systemDiffCode="A" systemCode="00" subSystemCode="0" subSubSystemCode="0" assyCode="00" disassyCode="00" disassyCodeVariant="A" infoCode="00W" infoCodeVariant="A" itemLocationCode="D" />
            <issueInfo issueNumber="000" inWork="01" />
            <language languageIsoCode="en" countryIsoCode="EN" />
          </dmRefIdent>
        </dmRef>
      </applicCrossRefTableRef>
      <applic id="appl-001">
        <displayText>
          <simplePara>MALE</simplePara>
        </displayText>
        <assert applicPropertyIdent="aircraft" applicPropertyType="prodattr" applicPropertyValues="MALE"/>
      </applic>
      <brexDmRef>
        <dmRef>
          <dmRefIdent>
            <dmCode modelIdentCode="MALE" systemDiffCode="A"
              systemCode="00" subSystemCode="0" subSubSystemCode="0"
              assyCode="00" disassyCode="00" disassyCodeVariant="A"
              infoCode="022" infoCodeVariant="A" itemLocationCode="D" />
          </dmRefIdent>
        </dmRef>
      </brexDmRef>
      <qualityAssurance>
        <unverified />
      </qualityAssurance>
    </dmStatus>
  </identAndStatusSection>
  <content>
    <description>
      <levelledPara>
        <title>Contents</title>
        <para>This document contains the information required to be furnished to end-user to obtain the flight safe and consist of 6 sections. Those sections provide approved information.</para>
        <para>
          The brief description of each section in this document are as follows:
          <randomList>
            <listItem>
              <para>Section 0 Introduction #ln; Introduce the FM General Information.#ln;</para>
            </listItem>
            <listItem>
              <para>Section 1 General #ln; Introduce the aircraft general information.#ln;</para>
            </listItem>
            <listItem>
              <para>Section 2 Limitation #ln; Describes the procedures requiring immediate flight crew action and procedures associated with failure of the systems or component.#ln;</para>
            </listItem>
            <listItem>
              <para>Section 3 Emergency and Abnormal Procedures #ln; Describes the procedures requiring emmediate flight crew action and procedures associated with failure of the systems or component.#ln;</para>
            </listItem>
            <listItem>
              <para>Section 4 Normal Procedures #ln; Describes about the procedures associated with systems that are functioning in their usual manner.#ln;</para>
            </listItem>
            <listItem>
              <para>Section 5 Performance #ln; Describes the aircraft performance information that required by the applicable regulation.#ln;</para>
            </listItem>
            <listItem>
              <para>Section 5 Weight and Balance #ln; Describes the instruction applicable to weight and balance control of the aircraft.#ln;</para>
            </listItem>
          </randomList>
        </para>
      </levelledPara>
      <levelledPara>
        <title>Publication Modules and Data</title>
        <para>To facilitate the most accurate and effective distribution of the latest infromation contained in this book, 
          the content is derived from a collection of electronically stored publication components called Data Modules (DM), while the Publication Modules (PM) is encase all Data modules to be produced. 
          DMs contain various amounts of information depending on the subject address for. When there any changes exist inside DMs, the entire DM is up-issued and distributed as the sum total of or as portion of this book using PM.</para>
        <para>
          PM and DM respectively is identified by a 17 and 22 characters prefixed by 'PMC' and 'DMC', separated by the hyphen '-'. They called by Pulication Module Code (PMC) and Data Module Code(DMC). When DM is in printed form, the title of this book is identified by the PMC and each page inside section is marked by DMC vertically on outside margin.</para>
      </levelledPara>
      <levelledPara>
        <title>Revisions</title>
        <para>Changes in this book shall be identified as follow:
          <sequentialList>
            <listItem>
              <para>Markings#ln;</para>
              <para>Addition or any changes in this content of book to existing data will be identified by vertical line, located outside margin of applicable page.#ln;</para>
              <para>The vertical line will only indicate the current change on each page. Physical relocation of data or the correction of typographical errors, outside of the material revised, will not be identified by a revision bar.#ln;</para>
            </listItem>
            <listItem>
              <para>Issue date#ln;</para>
              <para>At the title page, there will be the issue date of this book. At the bottom of each page, there will be the issue date of each data module#ln;</para>
            </listItem>
            <listItem>
              <para>Revision procedure#ln;</para>
              <para>To keep this book current, revision will be issued to the lates registered owner of airplane. Revisions to this book consist of:#ln;
                <randomList>
                  <listItem>
                    <para>List of Effective Data Modules (LEODM)</para>
                  </listItem>
                  <listItem>
                    <para>Change Highlights</para>
                  </listItem>
                  <listItem>
                    <para>Log og Revisions</para>
                  </listItem>
                  <listItem>
                    <para>New or Revised DMs</para>
                  </listItem>
                  <listItem>
                    <para>Temporary Revisions</para>
                  </listItem>
                </randomList>
              </para>
            </listItem>
          </sequentialList>
        </para>
        <levelledPara>
          <title>List of Effective Data Modules</title>
          <para>The list of Effective Data Modules (LOEDM) shows the revision number, date issued, and applicability aircraft. All DMs will be listed along with instruction which DM needs to be inserted in (new), replaced (changed), or deleted from this book.</para>
        </levelledPara>
        <levelledPara>
          <title>Change Highlights</title>
          <para>The change Highlights provide a dedicated overview of the changed, added and/or removed DMs with each revision.</para>
        </levelledPara>
        <levelledPara>
          <title>Log of Revisions</title>
          <para>The log of revisions provides a brief descriptions of each change that is introduced with a revision</para>
        </levelledPara>
        <levelledPara>
          <title>New or Revised Data Modules</title>
          <para>In accordance with the instruction of the LOEDM, new or revised DMs must be incorporated into the POH and superseded DMs destroyed.</para>
          <note noteType="note">
            <symbol infoEntityIdent="ICN-0001Z-00010-001-01.jpg" />
            <notePara>It is the owner or operator to maintain this book in a current status and incorporate successive revisions.</notePara>
          </note>
        </levelledPara>
        <levelledPara>
          <title>Temporary Revisions</title>
          <para>Temporary Revisions are issued when this book must be revised between the regular formal revisions. They are issued on yellow paper and recorded on the Log of Temporary Revisions. Temporary Revisions should normally be put at the front of this book. Apart from Section 9 Temporary Revision which should be put in front of the applicable supplement.</para>
          <para>Temporary Revision must only be removed from this book when instructed to do so by the Change Highlights of the next issue of a formal revision, when superseded by another temporary revision and sometimes by the incorporation of a Service Bulletion. The Log of Temporary Revisions ust be kept up to date by the owner or operator of aircraft.</para>
        </levelledPara>
      </levelledPara>
      <levelledPara>
        <title>Supplements</title>
        <para>Information required to operate the airplane when equipeed with specific functions is given in Supplements. A Supplements supersedes or substitutes the basic information given in this book. List of available Supplements is given in Section 9 of this book.</para>
      </levelledPara>
      <levelledPara>
        <title>Copyright and Legal Statement</title>
        <para>TBD</para>
      </levelledPara>
    </description>
  </content>
</dmodule>
